needscripts.com 2008-12-17

# Need Scripts: Web Development Resource: ASP, Flash, Java, JavaScripts, Perl, PHP, Visual Basics, XML, and more!

**Need Scripts Statement of Privacy**

Top Rank Position Network takes your privacy seriously. These privacy practices apply to Need Scripts and all other web sites operated under the title of Need Scripts and owned by Top Rank Position Network.

Information collected  
Unless mentioned/requested specifically, no personal information is collected by Top Rank Position Network. In any event, Top Rank Position Network does not collect or sell your name, address, email address, or phone number. Top Rank Position Network does use information about your browser and web surfing to determine what type of html codes to use to best serve you. Top Rank Position Network collects and stores the following information about you: the IP address or name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are coming from an America Online account, or yale.edu if you are connecting from a Yale domain): the date and time you access our site; the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site; and your Operating System and Browser. We use the information to measure the number of visitors to the sections of our site, which, in turn, helps us make our site more useful. The browser information is used to develop and code pages so most people will be able to view the site correctly.

Off-Site Links  
Once you access another Web site through an off-site link, whether to an advertiser or to an informational site, you are no longer on a Top Rank Position Network site, and are then subject to the privacy policy of the specific Web site containing that material.

Legal Disclaimer   
We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief, that such action is necessary in order to conform to the requirements of law or comply with legal process served on the Web site. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy  
Top Rank Position Network may change this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes, we will notify you by posting a prominent update on our pages.

Questions, comments  
Questions regarding this privacy statement, or regarding any other aspects of our network of Web sites, should be sent via e-mail to or to our offices at 6214 Masons Drive, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma - 73142. We read every message submitted and try to reply promptly to every one. We may also file your comments to improve the site and program, or review and discard the information.

Top Rank Position Network  
6214 Masons Drive  
Oklahoma City,  
Oklahoma - 73142

support@needscripts.com
